<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NSR1 on NO SOAP, RADIO</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/nsr1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NSR1 on NO SOAP, RADIO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:35:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/nsr1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Marylou Was a Bookkeeper&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/mary-lou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:35:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/mary-lou/</guid>
      <description>Stephanie Sutton is an Assistant Professor of Art at Winthrop University, specializing in photography and time-based media. Through the critical lenses of feminist theory, identity politics, and medical pathologies, her performances for the camera employ conventions of labor and ritual to complicate assumptions of discipline and destabilize virtues of self-control. The subject of several invitational shows, Sutton&amp;rsquo;s work is recognized for its success in transgressing the limits of the isolated subject and redirecting self-consciousness on to the viewer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Netherbox&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/netherbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:35:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/netherbox/</guid>
      <description>Erich Netherton is an Atlanta based percussionist and sound designer, he is known for his unique artistry that transcends traditional boundaries. His journey led him to craft an other wordly instrument called The Netherbox, a creation that reflects his innovative spirit and deep passion for music. Through his compositions, he invites audiences on a sonic adventure that resonates with their souls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;ウ​ル​ソ​ネ​ー​ト (Urusone​̄​to)&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/urusoneto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:35:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/urusoneto/</guid>
      <description>Urusonēto is a sound work by the french artist Wladimir Schall based on the Ursonate, also known as Sonata in Urlauten or the &amp;ldquo;Sonate of primitive sounds&amp;rdquo;, a phonetic poem composed between 1922 and 1932 by Kurt Schwitters and influenced by his meeting with Raoul Hausmann in 1921 in Prague, where he saw him reciting his poem &amp;ldquo;FMSBW&amp;rdquo;. (&amp;gt;See RH&amp;rsquo;s phonetic poems on Erratum Musical in 2019).&#xA;Wladimir Schall did not start reciting the poem himself, but preferred to entrust the task to &amp;ldquo;someone else&amp;rdquo;: the japanese voice of google translate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Strange Skills&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/strange-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:17:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/strange-skills/</guid>
      <description>Erstwhile 099&#xA;recorded at Third Hand, Seoul, Korea on Oct 7 &amp;amp; 8, 2023&#xA;concert organized by Rope Editions on Oct 7, 2023&#xA;recorded and mastered by Taku Unami&#xA;mixed by Devin Disanto&#xA;front cover photo by Devin DiSanto&#xA;inside center photo by Jung Yeon Cho&#xA;design by Yuko Zama&#xA;produced by Jon Abbey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;bot box boxes&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/bot-box-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:17:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/bot-box-boxes/</guid>
      <description>text here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Music For The Loud Air Conditioner&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/music-for-the-loud-air-conditioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:16:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/music-for-the-loud-air-conditioner/</guid>
      <description>Throughout May, 2020 the air conditioner outside my studio window in Austin, Texas went nuts. It was so loud that it was audible from the street, almost 200 meters away. Normally, my studio windows looked out onto a hectare of woods with birds and plants etc. Now everything was just the air conditioner.&#xA;There was no way to work without the air conditioner (the daytime heat would reach as high as 39 degrees Celsius), so I had to find a way to work with the air conditioner.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
